BRYAN **ARNDT**

WEB DEVELOPER



- 408-326-9504
- Bryan.Arndt52@gmail.com
- Q Coeur d'Alene, Idaho
- Github.com/bryanj408

SKILLS

- · Front-end Development
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- · Problem-Solving
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Career Foundry 2022

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS

North Idaho College 2020-2022

PROFILE

Web developer with a background in customer service. Experience in understanding the needs of the customer and crafting their vision into reality. A strong belief that there is more than one answer to a problem and the analytical skill and flexibility to find the best solution.

EXPERIENCE

PATIENT EQUIPMENT TRANSPORT

Kootenai Health

2018 - Present

Department needs vary greatly and were often under-staffed.

Worked with available team members to cut down on transport times, meet patient needs, and create better hospital-wide relations.

BOAT OPERATOR

New Sun Adventures

May 2018 - August 2018

Minimal staffing in a busy tourist-centric town. Navigating around time constraints and other boat rental companies, trained in logistics of boat operation and coordinating with customer's needs.

ESPRESSO MACHINE TECHNICIAN

Seattle Coffee Gear

2013 - 2017

Manufacturer issues required extensive testing and repair of highend super-automatic coffee machines. Explained technical matters clearly to customers and worked closely with manufacturers to promote educational training and decrease return repairs from 25% to 7% annually.